The Cotton Drifting
Chapter One, Jealousy
When They Cry
Behind where I looked back
(who's there in the front)?
I raised my nails in the dark
(and slashed the night).
Raindrops become droplets of
blood and drip down the throat.
If you don't have
a place to go back to...
...then stop here on my finger.
I'll take you away
along with that finger.
To the unopenable
forest where cicadas cry.
You can't turn back anymore.
（圭一(けいいち)）うん？
ち…遅刻！
I-I'm late!
ンンッ！
…てなんだ今日日曜だよ
Wait, today's Sunday.
Keiichi, you have
a call from Rena-chan!
（藍子(あいこ)）
圭一！レナちゃんから電話
Keiichi-kun! You're late!
（ﾚﾅ）圭一君遅いよ
（圭一）悪い悪い
Sorry, sorry...
Hey, where are
Satoko and Rika-chan?
あれ？沙都子(さとこ)と梨花ちゃんは？
（魅音(みおん)）あの２人は
街で合流したほうが早いから
It'll be faster if we
meet up in town.
そっか　ところで
街で部活ってどういうことだよ？
I see. By the way, why are we
having a club meeting in town?
それは行ってからのお楽しみ
（ﾚﾅ）あっ魅ぃちゃん待って
You'll see when you get there.
Mi-chan, wait!
（魅音･ﾚﾅ）ヤッホー！
Yoo-hoo!
Gee, why are there
so many kids at that toy store?
（圭一）しかし―
普通のおもちゃ屋に
なんでこんなに子供が？
Is there an event going
on there or something?
ひょっとして あの店で
今日 何かイベントでもあるのか？
そのとおり
なんと優勝賞金は５万円
Right, the grand prize
is fifty thousand yen!
F-Fifty thousand yen?
ご…５万円？
We were waiting for you all!
（沙都子）
皆さま方お待ちしてましてよ
（梨花(りか)）おはようございますです
Good morning.
んじゃ早速行ってみよう！
All right, let's go!
Game Tournament
So this is the site
for our club meeting, huh?
（圭一）…で
ここが部活の会場ってわけか？
I'm good friends with
the owner of this store.
私この店のおじさんと仲良しでね
たま～に客寄せイベントってことで
He sometimes lets us hold
tournaments to attract customers.
ゲーム大会を
開かせてもらってるんだよ
We have a lot
for today's meeting.
今日は大勢での部活なんだよ
The winner is free to do
what they want to the losers!
優勝者は負けたメンバーを
全員自由にしてよし
Bring it on.
上等だぜ
（店長）“犬も歩けば”―
Even a dog, after walking...
“くたびれる”
（ﾚﾅ）はい！
Yes!
はぅ～かぁいいよ…
It's so cute! I'll take it home!
お持ち帰り～！
Ronald as in President Reagan!
“ロンならレーガン大統領”
（沙都子）
フフフッ…いただきですわ
I got it.
（富田(とみた)）あっ…いつの間に？
（圭一）“トラップ沙都子”全開か
W-When...
Trap Satoko gives her all.
To a cute child,
good child, good child.
“かわいい子にはいい子いい子”
（富田）はい！
Got it.
Got it!
は～い
（富田）アワワッ…
（店長）
“花より団子(だんご)はダイエットの敵”
Sweet rice balls rather
than flowers are a diet's enemy.
Mi.
み～…
（岡村(おかむら)）ウオ～ッ！
エヘ～ッ…
（梨花）あっ取れましたですよ
Yay, I got it!
You're good, Rika-chan!
うまいよ梨花ちゃん
I can't compete...
かなわねえな…うん？
What?
何だよ？
（魅音）失望したよ
I'm let down.
You're the only one who's not
being serious like everyone else.
みんな本気なのに圭ちゃんだけは
本気になってくれないんだね
えっ？俺だって本気だよ
I'm being serious.
No, if you were...
いや本気の圭ちゃんなら―
...it'd be impossible not
to have one card by now.
まだカルタを１枚も
取れてないなんてことありえない
あれ？圭一君苦戦かな？かな？
（沙都子）ブザマですわね
Huh?
Keiichi-kun's not doing well?
How pathetic.
アッ…
（岡村）ウワッ…
Bathroom break for a second.
（圭一）ちょっと俺たちトイレ
（富田･岡村）ウワ～ッ…
Okay.
（圭一）富田君岡村君
取り引きしよう　俺を勝たせろ
Tomita-kun, Okamura-kun,
let's make a deal.
Help me win.
えっ…前原(まえばら)さん暴力はダメですよ
Maebara-san,
you can't beat us up.
話は最後まで聞け　まず富田君
君は沙都子萌(も)えだよな？
Listen to my plan.
First of all,
you like Satoko, right?
Don't deny it!
否定するな！
（富田）ヒイッ…
And Okamura-kun,
you like Rika, right?
そして岡村君
君は梨花萌えだよな？
へっ？
（圭一）赤くなるな！
Stop blushing!
俺が優勝したら…
２人を自由にしてよし
If I win, you can do
whatever you want with them!
（富田）アア…先輩！
（岡村）先輩が優勝決定です！
Senpai!
Senpai, you're the winner!
フッ…見てろよ
Just wait.
Bees attack crying faces.
（店長）“泣きっ面には８９10”
（魅音）は～い
Got it!
フゥ～…
（魅音）あっ…
（圭一）はい
Got it.
Good medicine hurts your wallet.
“良薬は財布に痛し”
Got it.
（梨花）はい
あたっ！
（圭一）はい
Got it.
Sorry.
すいません
フゥ～…
（圭一）はいはいはい！
Got it. Got it. Got it.
（富田）おっと！
（圭一）はいはいはい！
Got it. Got it. Got it.
（岡村）フゥフゥ～！
（富田）ウワ～ッ…
Got it!
（圭一）はい～！
Good for you.
I'm a little impressed.
やるじゃない 圭ちゃん
ちょっとは見直したよ
（圭一）フッ…
俺が本気を出せばこんなもんよ
That's what happens
when I get serious.
（少年）すげえ…
まあ
敵ながらあっぱれってとこだね
Well, I guess you were
a pretty worthy opponent...
Unfortunately, as of now,
it looks like I'm tied with you.
不本意ながら今のとこ
圭ちゃんと私は同点みたいだよ
Mister, please read the last card.
おじさん
最後のカルタを読み上げてくれ
Okay.
Wait a minute!
（魅音）ちょっと待った！
（圭一）うん？
この勝負ここまで　あとは
園崎(そのざき)魅音に預からせてもらうよ
That's it for this. Postponed
by order of Mion Sonozaki.
な…なに？
W-What?
Hey, Mion!
Are you running away?
こら魅音！逃げる気か？
ごめん圭ちゃん
私これからバイトなんだよね
Sorry, Kei-chan,
I have work now.
バイト？そんなの聞いてないぞ！
Work? I didn't hear about that!
（店長）まあまあ
優勝賞金は次回に回すとして
Now, now.
The prize money
will be carried over.
You can have this for today.
今日のところはこれで
わあ…何かな？かな？
（圭一）うん？
What could it be? What?
ええっ？何だよ？これ
What's this?
あらあら
かわいいのが出てきましたわよ
My, my, it seems
something cute came out.
わあ…いいないいな　お持ち帰り
Lucky, lucky.
I want to take it home!
ハハハハッ…圭ちゃんには
似合わない物もらったね
You got something
not suited for you.
どうせ…
Whatever... You can have it.
やるよ
（ﾚﾅ）えっ？くれるの？レナに
You're giving it to me?
かわいい物といえばレナだろう
Cute things are your thing.
Thank you!
ありがとう！はぅ～…
俺が
こんなの持っててもしかたないし
It'd be useless if I kept it.
You don't seem
like the type either.
お前も似合わないタイプだしな
あ…ああよく分かってるじゃない
You're so right.
私もさ“どうして男に
生まれなかったんだろう”って―
Sometimes I wonder
why I wasn't born a guy.
思うときあるんだよね
アハハハッ…
オッ…よく分かってんじゃん
Good, you know it too.
Later, all. See you tomorrow.
んじゃねみんなまたあした
（圭一）おう
- Yeah!
- Bye-bye!
（ﾚﾅ）バイバ～イ
ハハッ…あっ俺腹減ったな
何か食ってかね？
I'm hungry.
Want to eat somewhere?
ごめん
レナはお夕飯の支度があるから
Sorry, I have to prepare dinner.
ボクたちもお買い物して
帰らないとダメなのです
And we have to go
shopping before we get home.
Too bad.
残念ですわ
そっか　じゃまたあしたな
I see. Well, see you tomorrow.
（圭一）
へえ…結構ちゃんとしてんじゃん
Wow, this place is pretty nice.
W-W-Welcome.
（ｳｴｰﾄﾚｽ）
い…いら…いらっしゃいませ
Is she new?
新米か？まあだけど
この制服はなかなか悪くない…
But the uniform isn't too bad...
えっ…魅音？
Mion? Is that you?
…だよな？
お前バイトってこのことか？
Is this your job?
U-Um...
あ…あの…
待てよ　ここでは俺は客
Wait.
I'm a customer, so that makes
me superior to the waitress.
ウエートレスより
上の立場なわけだよな
しかしこうして見ると結構
そういう服も似合ってるじゃん
Well, you don't look
so bad in those clothes.
あっ…恥ずかしいんだから
その…あまり見ないでよ
It's embarrassing,
so don't stare so much.
恥ずかしがったフリしてもダメだぜ
Pretending to be
embarrassed won't work.
魅音はそういう恥ずかしい格好で
男の目を引いて楽しんでるんだろう
You enjoy guys' attention by
dressing like that, don't you?
わ…私だってその…
好きでこんなことしてるわけじゃ
I-I'm not doing
this because I like...
I bet that outfit
disappoints your mom.
そ～んな恥ずかしい格好して
お母さん悲しんでるぞ
No!
そんな！
またその見えそうで見えないのが
最高だよなウヘヘヘッ…
Plus, how I can't quite
see it is awesome.
イヤ～！
（圭一）おやおや？
No!
Hey, hey!
Since I'm a customer here,
you should serve me more.
お客さまへの奉仕の心が
まだまだでおじゃるぞよ
どうかお許しを…
Please forgive me.
I want to take you home!
お持ち帰り～！
（殴る音）
それはイヤ！
I don't want that!
ヘッ…
今日はこのくらいで許してやろう
I'll let you go for today.
But to think the almighty
Mion Sonozaki is waiting tables...
しかし天下御免の園崎魅音が
ウエートレスが苦手とはな
あの…
Um...
だ…だから違うんです
（圭一）違うって？
I-I think you're mistaken.
Mistaken?
私…魅音じゃないんです
I'm not Mion.
Um, I'm Shion Sonozaki,
Mion's younger twin sister.
あの…私…
園崎詩音(しおん)　魅音の双子の妹なんです
Twin?
双子？
はいよくお姉に間違われるんです
Yes, I get mistaken
for my sister a lot.
But you acted as if
we knew each other.
でもさっき
初対面とは思えない反応したよな
T-That's because my sister
always talks about you...
そ…それは…
いつもお姉が話している人だから
知ってたわけで…
...so I knew you.
ふ～ん…
そっか　悪かったな疑ったりして
I see.
Sorry for not believing you.
いえ分かってくれればいいんです
お姉も敵の多い人ですから
Not at all.
It's fine if you understand.
My sister has
a lot of enemies, so...
ウフッ…
（ｳｴｰﾄﾚｽ）園崎さん
“Ｒ”入っちゃっていいですよ
Sonozaki-san,
you can go on break.
あっはい
Okay!
じゃ私はこれで
Well, I'm off now.
It was fun talking to
the often-mentioned Kei-chan.
ウワサの“圭ちゃん”と話せて
楽しかったです
あっ…
お姉と同じ呼び方でいいですよね？
Is it okay to address
you like my sister does?
ハァ…
魅音のヤツすっかり化けやがって
Mion was sure trying
to be someone else.
What does she
mean by her sister, Shion?
なにが“妹の詩音です”だ
When They Cry
（魅音）へえ…
Your parents aren't home today?
今日お父さんも
お母さんもいないんだ？
ああ
育ち盛りの息子を放ったらかしとは
Leaving a maturing
boy home alone...
They're evil parents.
まったく鬼親だぜ
（魅音）
アハハハッ…文句言わないの
Don't complain.
Anyway, I'll see you tomorrow.
じゃまたあした
Work again?
（ﾚﾅ）今日もバイト？
Yeah, going in early
till I'm used to it.
そう　慣れないうちは
早めに来いって言われてんだ
I guess being a waitress is tough.
やっぱ
ウエートレスって大変なんだな
えっ？魅ぃちゃん
ウエートレスさんやってるの？
You're a waitress?
違う違う！私はおもちゃ屋
おじさんに店番頼まれちゃってさ
No, no! I work at a toy store.
My uncle wants me to help out.
Shion's the waitress.
ウエートレスやってるのは
詩音のほう
ああごめんごめん間違えた
Oh, sorry, I messed up.
詩音って誰かな？
Shion? Who's that?
Oh, Mion's twin sister, but their
personalities are nothing alike.
ああ魅音の双子の妹なんだけど
性格は全然違うんだ
そうそう外見は似てるんだけど
性格は大違いでね
Yeah, yeah!
We look alike,
but we're totally different.
私は
優しくて思いやりある性格だけど
I'm the nice, caring one,
while Shion is cold and harsh.
詩音は
冷めてておっかないんだよね
アハハハハッ！
（ﾚﾅ）へえ…
I didn't know you had a sister...
魅ぃちゃんに妹がいるなんて
知らなかったよ
お家(うち)に行っても
会ったことなかったし
I never saw her at your house.
ハッ！えっと…そのその…
Um, well, well...
You know I'm the only
one with Grandma.
ほら知ってるでしょう？
ばっちゃと住んでるの私だけだから
詩音は興宮(おきのみや)の実家に住んでるの
Shion lives in Okinomiya.
We're not that close,
so she doesn't visit much.
あんまり仲良くないから
行き来もそんなにないしさ
ふ～ん…レナも会ってみたいな
どこのお店で働いてるのかな？
I'd like to meet her.
Where does she work?
あっ…いやその…
Um, uh...
あっごめん！バイト急がないと
Oh, sorry! I have to get to work.
じゃあね
レナに圭ちゃんまたあした！
Rena, Kei-chan,
see you tomorrow!
Tomorrow, tomorrow, tomorrow...
あした～あした～
She ran.
（圭一）逃げたな
（ﾚﾅ）変な魅ぃちゃん
She's weird.
But she was acting kind of cute.
でも
魅ぃちゃんなんだかかわいかった
I wonder why. I wonder why.
なんでかな？なんでかな？フフ…
（圭一）うん？
ハァ…腹減った～
I'm hungry...
（ドアチャイム）
は～い
Yes? The door's open.
開いてますよ
Hello... huh?
こんにちは…て！
Kei-chan, what are you doing?
圭ちゃん 何やってんですか？
あっあの…魅…詩…
U-Um, Mi... Shi...
ああもう！ン～ッ…何の用？
Forget it!
What is it?
（詩音）はいこれ
Here.
えっ？もしかしてこれ…
Is this...
お姉が電話してきて
My sister called saying
that Kei-chan was starving...
圭ちゃんひもじい思いしてるから
何か差し入れしてやればって
...and that I should
bring something.
うれしいけど…なんで？
（詩音）あっ…
I'm grateful, but why?
Um, well...
あの…その…
圭ちゃんお店のお客さんだし
Since you're a customer.
客？
Customer?
W-Well, I have
to go to work now.
そ…それじゃ
私バイトに行くから
オオッ！うまそう
Wow, it looks delicious!
It better not be
poisoned or anything...
毒とか入ってんじゃないんだろうか
（おなかの鳴る音）
くそ－！
Crap!
If that happens, it happens!
そんときゃそんときだ！
んっ！うまい
Yum.
（圭一）…で
今日のゲームは何だ？
So what'll we play today?
それよりレナは―
Before that, we should decide
on today's punishment game.
“今日の罰ゲームは
何かな”のほうが先だと思うな
ヘヘッ…レナは分かってるね
Rena understands.
今日も
飛びっ切りのを用意してるよ！
Today will be another crazy one!
Sorry, I have something
else I need to do.
ごめんなさいです
ボクは ちょっと
やりたいことがありますです
（魅音）どうしたの？
What happened?
Right, you have to practice
for the cotton drifting.
あっそうか綿流しの練習だね
Yes, it's this coming Sunday.
そうですわよ　今度の日曜ですもの
梨花は猛特訓中なのですわよ
Rika's been
practicing really hard.
I see.
Then we'll cancel today's club.
（魅音）
そっか　じゃ今日の部活は中止だね
I'm sorry, but I will do my best.
ごめんなさいなのです
でも頑張りますですよ
（魅音）うん
（ﾚﾅ）みんな応援してるからね
We're all cheering for you.
Is she practicing
for some competition?
梨花ちゃん
何か大会前とかなのか？
梨花ちゃんは
綿流しの巫女(みこ)さんだからね
She's the Cotton Drifting
Festival's shrine maiden.
その練習
（圭一）綿流し？
It's for that.
Cotton drifting?
圭ちゃん家(ち)には
回覧板とか行ってないの？
Don't you get newsletters
at your house?
Next Sunday is
the Cotton Drifting Festival.
今度の日曜日は綿流しのお祭り
（圭一）ああそういえば
Oh, now that you mention it,
I think my mom talked about it.
そんなようなことを
おふくろが言ってたような
しっかりしてよね
（ﾚﾅ）フフッ…
Pay attention a bit.
綿流しのメーン儀式で巫女さんが
やる奉納の舞っていうのを―
She'll do the Dance of Hounou,
the festival's main ceremony.
梨花ちゃんがやるんだよ
（魅音）そうそう
Right, you dance holding a hoe,
but since it's really heavy...
鍬(くわ)を持って舞を踊るんだけど
その鍬がすんごく重いらしくて
...she said she practices
with a mallet for mochi rice.
梨花ちゃん “餅つき用の杵(きね)持って
練習してるんだ”って言ってた
へえ…梨花ちゃんって
結構力持ちなんだな
Rika-chan must be pretty strong.
人は見かけによらないってことか
You can't judge by one's looks.
フフッ…
見かけとは逆が誠かもしれないよ
The opposite of how you look
might be closer to the truth.
フフッ…
面白いことを言うじゃねえか
Interesting point.
あっ！いっけねえ
私も今日バイトだ
Oh no! I have work today too!
先帰るね
（ﾚﾅ）あっ…
I have to go.
Okay, bye-bye.
Since you can't judge by looks...
人は見かけによらないってことは
...does that mean Mion's
really a nice person?
あの魅音も
実はいい人だってことか？
She's a nice person.
魅ぃちゃんはいい人だよ
She always tries to be a leader,
but she's a really cute girl.
いっつもみんなのリーダーとして
頑張ってるけど
ホントは
とってもかわいい女の子なんだよ
Cute girl?
かわいい女の子？
フフッ…確かにそうかもな
That could be true.
Did I wash it out?
ちゃんと洗ったよな？
うんＯＫフフッ…
Okay.
あいて…オワッ！
Ouch.
Ow...
What the hell are you doing?
（不良１）何すんだ？この野郎
Say something!
すっとぼけてんじゃねえよ！
すす…すいません
ちょっと足が引っ掛かって…
S-S-Sorry,
my legs got caught a little...
That's not a little!
（不良２）
ちょっとじゃねえだろうが！
The paint's scratched.
（不良３）
塗装剥げてんじゃねえか
What'll you do about this, huh?
どうしてくれんだよ？
Shut up, you damn bastards.
やかましいよくそボケどもが
Who are you?
んだ？てめえ
圭ちゃん離してとっととうせな！
（圭一）ハッ…
Let go of Kei-chan and beat it!
くそ女が…
Bitch...
み…魅音！
M-Mion!
な…何だ？こいつら
W-Who are they?
Who are you guys?
何だ？お前ら
W-What's going on?
ど…どうなってんだよ？
H-How should I know?
し…知るか
Thanks for your help.
（圭一）さっきは本当に
ありがとうな　詩音は勇敢だな
You're brave.
I was scared too.
（詩音）私だって怖かったですよ
But since you were in trouble...
でも
ほかならぬ圭ちゃんのピンチだし
...I gathered my courage
and tried my best.
勇気出して
頑張りましたってことです
ハハッ…だけどさ驚いたな
人がどんどん集まってきて
But I was surprised when
all those people gathered up.
あれ全部雛見沢(ひなみざわ)の人？
They're from Hinamizawa?
Yes, the villagers
are united tightly.
ええそうです　雛見沢の人は
みんな結束してるんです
１人の敵は全員の敵ですから
One enemy is everyone's enemy.
Sounds like a mafia family.
（圭一）
まるでマフィアの一族みたいだな
（詩音）フフッ…
そんなこと言っちゃダメですよ
Don't say that.
It's a very good thing.
とても
ありがたいことなんですから
圭ちゃんも感謝の気持ちを忘れずに
You shouldn't
forget to be grateful.
（圭一）感謝ならしてるって
今日も…それに昨日のお弁当も
I'm grateful.
For today and
for yesterday's lunch.
Lunch?
お弁当？私そんなこと…
I didn't...
ううん何でもないです
おいしかったですか？
Never mind.
Was it good?
Of course!
うんそりゃもう
ウフフッ…こうしてると
なんかデートみたいですね
It feels like we're on a date.
イヤですか？
（圭一）えっ…
You don't like it?
私お姉がどうして圭ちゃんのこと
好きなのか分かった気がします
I think I know why
my sister likes you.
Say, is it all right if
I like you a little bit too?
ねえ…圭ちゃんのことちょっぴり
好きになってもいいですか？
あ…あのあの…俺俺俺…
U-Um, um... l-I... I...
S-Shion...
No, Mion...
It's true you can't
judge one by their looks.
人は見かけによらないって本当だな
魅音にも女の子らしいとこが
たくさんあるってこと―
I understand now that you
have a girly side too, Mion...
よく分かったからさ
（詩音）えっ？
もう
双子の妹なんて作り話ししなくても
...so you don't have
to lie about having a twin.
Bye-bye!
（少年）バイバ～イ
Thanks! Come again!
ありがとう　また来てね
M-Mion!
み…魅音！
け…圭ちゃん！
K-Kei-chan?
Y-You really are twins?
ほ…本当に…
双子ーっ！
Didn't I say so?
だから 言ったじゃないですか
（圭一）ハァ…
B-Bathroom!
ト…トイレ
（ﾚﾅ）あっ…待ってよ魅ぃちゃん
Wait, Mi-chan!
That's her fifteenth time
to the bathroom.
（沙都子）
これでトイレ１５回目ですわ
Mion-san is
definitely weird today.
今日の魅音さん
徹底的に変ですわね
There are times when
girls become unstable.
女の子は
不安定になるときもあるのです
一部始終を知ってはいるんだが
何とも説明しづらい
Even though I know the whole
story, it's hard to explain.
Keiichi-kun.
（ﾚﾅ）圭一君
（圭一）うん？
Um, well, it seems like
you've had a rough time.
えっとその…
災難だったみたいだね
I didn't think Shion really existed.
まさか詩音が実在したとは
しかも弁当作ってきたのは
詩音のフリした魅音だったなんてな
Plus, Mion brought me
lunch disguised as Shion.
魅ぃちゃんかなり壊れてたけど
なんとか直したところだから
Mi-chan was really broken,
but I finally fixed her.
Fixed her? How?
直したって…どうやって？
テレビと同じ
斜め４５度くらいの角度で―
Just like a TV. I went like
this from a 45 degree angle!
エイッ エイッて
（圭一）ハァ…
でね圭一君にも
お願いしたいことがあるの
And I also have
a favor to ask of you.
A favor?
お願い？
（ﾚﾅ）うん魅ぃちゃんはね
She's decided to forget
what happened yesterday.
昨日までのことを
なかったことにするから―
Can you do the same?
圭一君も
なかったことにしてあげて
でも圭一君も分かったでしょう？
But you see now that Mi-chan
has a cute side too, right?
魅ぃちゃんにも
かわいい所があるんだって
ああ退屈しないヤツだと
いうことは分かった
Yeah, I know she's someone
you won't get tired of.
うん？沙都子梨花ちゃん
Satoko? Rika-chan?
You and she have learned a lot.
圭一も魅ぃもいっぱいいっぱい
お勉強しましたですね
きっと
圭一はステキな大人になれますよ
You'll become
a very fine adult someday.
Yeah, and since you study hard,
it seems you'll be a fine adult too.
ああ梨花ちゃんもお勉強家だから
すごいステキな大人になれそうだな
Of course.
もちろんなのです
When I'm an adult,
I'll be a truly great adult.
ボクは大人になったら
すごいすごいなのです
Well, when I'm an adult,
I'll be a splendid lady.
あ～ら私も大人になったら
すごいレディーになるんですのよ
You'll be yourself
no matter how old you are.
沙都子は
いくつになっても沙都子だと思うぞ
なんですって！
What's that?
Ow! What the heck
are you doing, Satoko?
いてっ！何しやがんだ沙都子！
（沙都子）ア～ハッハッ！
To get my happiness,
I had done everything...
...but had done nothing
to be blamed and accused of.
The sound of footsteps
became louder every day.
Then I noticed the fact
there was no time.
I was a believer in life,
to be myself always.
And was asking
whether I would be alive.
Give me a reason
why not to adopt in this way.
Or judge me to be guilty
of so many incurable sins.
Tell me why or why not?
Complaining way too much.
Maybe I overlooked
something fatal for me.
Preview
What I want to see
is the shape in the dark.
（ﾅﾚｰﾀｰ）見たいのは闇の中の形
What I want to hear
are the hesitating footfalls.
知りたいのは本当の居場所
What I want to know
is where I really belong.
「ひぐらしのなく頃に」
When They Cry.
The Cotton Drifting
Chapter 2, Takano.
Chapter 2, Takano
The Cotton Drifting
Chapter 2, Takano.
Can you believe it?
あなたは信じられますか？